Guide to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello RG.006
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series XII: Addendum II
  - Subseries D: Publications & Notes
    - LC Science Tracer Bulletin, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Peace, Welfare and Security for Mankind through Educations, 1975 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - The City as an Adaptive Entity, 1999 (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Technological Innovation, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Technological Forecasting, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Toward a Check List for Human Factors in Environmental Engineering, undated (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Prospectives in Bioengineering Research for Civil Engineers, undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Stochastic Simulation of Convective Diffusion in the Axial Plasmatic Gaps of Capillaries, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Publications not by Bugliarello, 1962-1984 (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Notes- Poly Endowment, undated (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Notes- Nassau County Dinners, undated (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous drafts and notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Comments on conference, undated (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous notes, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Notes, undated (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Notebooks, 1956 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  - Subseries E: Correspondence
    - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1970s, 1971-1979 (Box 51, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, 1990s, 1991-1999 (Box 51, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  - Subseries F: Clippings
    - Clippings, 1970s, 1973-1977 (Box 51, Folder 53)
    - Clippings, Poly-Long Island, 1975-1979 (Box 51, Folder 54)
    - Clippings, 1980s, 1982-1989 (Box 51, Folder 55)
    - Clippings, 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 51, Folder 56)
    - Clippings, 2000s, 2007-2011 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  - Subseries G: Polytechnic documents
    - Student aid grant summary and Expenditure report, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 58)
    - Application for reserach grant, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968-1975; undated (Box 51, Folder 60)
  - Subseries H: Memorada, Newsletters, & Brochures
    - Memorada and News Releases, 1990-1994 (Box 41, Folder 61)
    - Newsletters, 1974-1989 (Box 51, Folder 62)
    - Conference Programs, 1960s, 1965-1969 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Conference Programs, 1970s, 1972-1977 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Conference Programs, 1980s, 1987-1999; 1987-1989 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic Brochures and Commencement Programs, 1975-2013 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Brochures and Publications, 1966-1997 (Box 54)
  - Subseries I: MetroTech model
    The MetroTech model was commissioned by Forest City Ratner by Real Models, Inc. Atlanta. It is on loan from Virigina Bugliarello.
  - Subseries J: Polytechnic Commencement robe, undated (Box 55)
- Series XIII: 2022 Accretion, 1971-1980
  These items are a 2022 accretion to the Administrative Papers of the President George Bugliarello and consist of papers as well as publications written or edited by Bugliarello. These items had been pulled from the collection and set aside as possible duplicates. Upon closer inspection, unique items were identified, resulting in this accretion. This accretion is located on bay 28, shelf 5E.
  - Sub-series A: Inauguration, 1974-1975
    - Inauguration (I), 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Inauguration (II), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Sub-series B: Publications, 1971-1980
    - Science Advice to the President edited by George Bugliarello, et al., 1980 (Box 57, Item 1)
    - Women in Engineering: Bridging the Gap Between Society and Technology edited by George Bugliarello, et al, 1971 (Box 57, Item 2)